const questions = [
    {
        'question': 'What other actress was considered for the role of Scully?',
        'options':['Pamela Anderson', 'Jenny McCarthy', 'Debra Messing', 'Helen Hunt'],
        'answer': 0
    },
    {
        'question': 'Which of the following is true about the cigarette smoking man?',
        'options': ['He was originally supposed to be Scully and Mulder\'s boss.', 'He was supposed to be Mulder\'s father.', 'He was supposed to be an alien',
        'He was originally cas as an extra'],
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': 'What is the name of the computer hacking group that assists Mulder with research?',
        'options': ['The 4 Horsemen', 'Ufologists', 'The Lone Gunmen',
        'The Mr Robots'],
        'answer': 0
    },
    {
        'question': 'What other actor was considered to play the part of Mulder',
        'options': ['Dean Cain', 'Tom Cruise', 'Alec Baldwin',
        'David Caruso'],
        'answer': 0
    },
    {
        'question': 'This present day invention was first found on X Files over a decade before it was released as a product.',
        'options': ['Smart Car', 'Smart Home', 'Smart Watch',
        'DVR'],
        'answer': 1
    },
    {
        'question': 'This episode was based on the following real life phenomenon...',
        'options': ['The episode where an FBI agent is believed to be abducted.', 'The episode where certain parts of the ocean cause accelerated aging.', 'The episode where a mysterious bird like creature is believed to kill people at random.', 'The one about the Chupacabra.'],
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': 'This unknown actor was featured before they became famous...',
        'options': ['James Vanderbeek', 'Jack Black', 'Jason Biggs', 'Don Cheadle'],
        'answer': 1
    },
    {
        'question': 'What was Scully\'s daughter\'s name?',
        'options': ['Carol', 'Brenda', 'She never had a daughter', 'Laura'],
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': 'How did the lone gunmen meet?',
        'options': ['They worked together', 'At a trade show', 'They were organized by Mulder', 'At a JFK study group'],
        'answer': 0
    },
    {
        'question': 'What happened to Sam Mulder',
        'options': ['She died', 'She was abducted', 'She was taken away by her father', 'SHe ran away from home'],
        'answer': 2
    },
    {
        'question': 'What did Mulder\'s dad do for a living',
        'options': ['He was a garbage man.', 'He worked for the CIA.', 'He was unemployed.', 'He worked for the FBI.'],
        'answer': 3
    },
    {
        'question': 'Did Mulder ever have a girlfriend?',
        'options': ['Yes, he was in love with the bug lady.', 'He had no girlfriends.', 'He dated an agent out of the academy.', 'He always secretly dated Scully'],
        'answer': 2
    },
    {
        'question': 'What Breaking Bad actor was in an episode?',
        'options': ['Brian Cranston', 'Aaron Paul', 'Saul Goodman', 'Taco'],
        'answer': 2
    }

]